The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The Four Sect Alliance opens its gates !
We recruit all kinds of cultivators, rogue, demonic, orthodox.
Join us to prepare for war.
If you don't come,
you will suffer the consequences !
A heavy snow has been falling
day and night.
In a single month,
the mortal world has begun to collapse.
The cultivators of the Four Sect Alliance
have tried to stop the snow from falling.
They have also tried to use spells to clear the snow
but they all failed.
In the end,
The cultivators ordered the mortal emperor
to summon a large number of mortals to clear the snow themselves.
We need to go clear the snow.
Those who disobey will be killed...
You can't bring these things with you.
Take this with you and keep it close to your body.
Okay.
Uncle Wang,
it's cold outside.
Remember to keep some firewood at home.
Go back inside !
Keep up !
Let's go.
Quick !
Keep up.
What's this nonsense ?
Hurry up !
We haven't met in more than 10 years.
Fellow cultivator Zhou still looks the same.
Brother Wang,
you have indeed gone farther than I have.
It seems that I
have been marching in place, without progressing my domain.
You already finished carving Master Qing Song's
Passing of Time Domain.
This wood carving in Brother's hands
is a top quality artifact for Nascent Soul cultivators.
You have improved so much
in a mere 10 years.
I admire you.
If you like it,
I can give it to you.
Brother Wang,
thank you.
With this wood carving,
I may use the Passing of Time Domain to reach Soul Formation.
But...
I admit defeat, don't give me another obsession.
I don't want this wood carving anymore.
You can have this jade,
it contains a Soul Formation spell.
If that's the case, I won't tempt you anymore.
With the shortcut in front of him,
he chose to keep his Dao Heart
and pursue his own domain.
He isn't the kind
that gives up easily.
Brother Wang,
have you noticed
anything strange about this snow ?
This snow
is not natural.
Correct.
There is killing intent inside the snow.
It's the magic of Xue Yue cultivators.
Xue Yue cultivators ?
Xue Yue is a rank 4 cultivation country in the North of Suzaku.
The cultivation methods of Xue Yue
involve this magical snow.
When the Xue Yue attacks a country,
they use a one way formation to cover the country in snow.
The day the Four Sect Alliance is completely covered in snow,
will be the day Xue Yue attacks.
Brother Wang, please look.
I'm not kidding,
this snow
will not melt.
I am here today
on behalf of the Four Sect Alliance
to invite Brother Wang to join us in this war.
Your cultivation,
is just a breath away from a breakthrough.
Once you join us,
the Four Sect Alliance's strength will increase greatly.
Brother Zhou,
I won't see you off.
The Four Sect Alliance is a thousand years old rank 4 country.
If you are willing to join,
I will grant any request that is within my power.
Will you at least consider it ?
Brother Wang, what's the meaning of this ?
Xue Yue comes from the other side of the planet.
Why are they invading here and not somewhere else ?
Since Brother Zhou doesn't want to tell me,
then I will not ask about it.
If you are willing to join the war,
I will tell you the truth.
Please.
Brother Zhou,
since this person is not willing to join the Four Sect Alliance,
You Kong\NBlack Soul Sect Elder\NLate stage Nascent Soul
the order is to execute him with no mercy.
Why didn't you do it !?
This person has carvings of my White Cloud Sect Elders.
If you want to go, then go.
But I'm not looking for death.
You Huan\NBlack Soul Sect Elder\NLate stage Nascent Soul
So you really are afraid of him !
The three of us are the same cultivation level as him.
You Mie\NBlack Soul Sect Elder\NLate stage Nascent Soul
If we use a formation,
he will die for sure.
Ink Bone Sword Formation,
activate !
It has been more than 30 years...
He destroyed our formation !?
Who...
Who the hell are you !?
You shouldn't have provoked me.
Brother Zhou,
come and help me !
what are you doing !?
You angered Brother Wang,
how could I let you leave ?
Brother Wang, don't worry.
These three died at the hands of Xue Yue.
This person should forever stay a friend,
not an enemy.
Middle of the night and some brats woke me up by fighting outside !
I had finally found a good spot to sleep in...
I’m really unlucky.
Warm up your body.
You are a good kid.
But...
I won't share my roasted chicken !
I needed wine with it.
Not bad, kid.
Soul Formation is not far away.
The Four Sect Alliance is chaotic right now.
Hurry up and reach Soul Formation !
Otherwise, with your cultivation,
you won't get anything good out of it.
Does Senior know what is happening with the Four Sect Alliance ?
A Four Sect Alliance cultivator
stole a Rain Cauldron that belonged to Xue Yue.
So they are here to take it back.
It's a small matter.
Rain Cauldron ?
Tell your King
to send the Rain Cauldron to my temple in 3 days
And I won't pursue this matter.
Speaking of this Rain Cauldron, to be honest,
there is more than one.
But it is useless on its own.
However, the day the Celestial Gates open,
the Rain Cauldron will grant you access to the Celestial Realm
by using one of the 4 gates: Wind, Rain, Thunder, Lightning.
To enter the Celestial Realm ?
No wonder they fight over it.
What ?
Are you interested now ?
Sadly,
all the Ancient Celestials are gone.
They all died in battle.
The current Celestial Realm
is empty.
They all died ?
Of course they're all dead !
Otherwise, why do you think
Soul Transformation and above cultivators
are still around in this world ?
It's because...
they have nowhere else to go !
The Ancient Gods are all dead,
the Ancient Celestials are all dead.
There aren't many ancient cultivators left
which is why the Cultivation Alliance appeared.
If that's the truth,
why are they fighting over the Rain Cauldron to enter it ?
The Celestial Realm is shattered in 4 pieces.
The 4 gates just lead to different sections of the Celestial Realm.
Although the Celestial Realm is shattered,
there are still many ancient artifacts in it.
It's pretty good stuff !
But the most important
is the celestial spiritual energy !
To reach Soul Transformation
without a Soul Transformation Pill
you need to absorb celestial spiritual energy to breakthrough.
Senior is very knowledgeable about the world,
you are so smart.
Junior admires you.
I admire you.
I came today to request a wood carving of myself.
I'll give it to Xiao Cui from the Pink Pavillon !
That way she will always remember me...
After I promised Senior,
I've tried to carve you many times.
This is it !
Yes yes yes !
It looks like me !
It's the real me !
Your wood carving
has yet to match my handsomeness
but you're getting close to it.
It's completely negligible.
As long as Senior is satisfied.
You carved me well.
I will let you borrow
that straw hat for a while longer.
There are still 99 wood carvings left.
Don't forget them when you reach Soul Formation !
Otherwise,
no matter where you go,
this old man will find you.
I will not forget
the promise I made to Senior.
In this war between Xue Yue and the Four Sect Alliance,
the Rain Cauldron is just a pretext.
The real reason is the annexation of this country.
There is an even higher-level cultivation country involved.
Kid,
you have to be careful.
The lights of thousands of families
withered in an instant.
Everything in the world is meant to die.
In my life,
death
has been the shadow following me.
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
The first person I killed
was Sun Dazhu.
He took me as his disciple,
poisoned me
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
and almost killed me.
Then I killed Bai Zhan,
he deserved it.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
Teng Li's arrogance
and like many other unseparable things.
led me to a 400 years long killing spree.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
Wang Lin !
These 400 years of killing
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
have taught me
the meaning of Death.
Death
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
I don't hate killing anymore,
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
killing is what made my life what it is.
Death...
I am Death.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
But this vast world
is not only about cultivating and killing.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Under this sky,
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
there are many living beings.
Uncle Wang !
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
I'm Da Niu.
This is for you !
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
Uncle Wang,
I brought you some wine !
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
These 30 years of turning mortal
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
have taught me the meaning of Life.
I am Death
and I am also Life.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
Rather than cultivating for thousands of years,
it was living the life of a mortal that made me realize
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.
who I really am.
Uncle Niu,
why are you still awake ?
I don't know how my wife is doing.
And also Uncle Wang...
I wanted Uncle Wang to get a little bit older
to have him stop wood carving
and serve him for his last years.
This snow has been going on for too long.
There is no ending to this.
We must look ahead !
Uncle Niu, let's move to another country.
I heard it's not snowing there.
It's already spring there.
Nature is blossoming
and the sun is bright and beautiful...
Get up !
The kid...
He froze... to death ?
Hurry up and get to work !
It's none of your business
if the others are dead !
Hurry up !
Uncle Wang !
My dear wife !
Xiao Niu !
Don't be afraid,
I'm here to save you !
I will take you to another country !
There is no way out.
There is no way out...
My wife...
Xiao Niu...
Uncle Wang...
Da Niu,
it's okay.
Uncle Wang is here.
Uncle Wang...?
You...
really are
an Immortal ?
There's no need to be afraid.
Let's go.
I'll take you
to find your family.
Where am I ?
My dear husband ?
Dad, Mom !
Xiao Niu ?
Have a look !
We're outside !
We're really...
in another country !
Why are we here ?
I remember I was still inside the house
when I fell asleep.
It was Uncle Wang that saved us.
Uncle Wang ?
Uncle Wang,
thank you.
Take care of yourself.
The time of Soul Formation has come.
I only need to go in seclusion for 10 years.
But the opportunity to get a Rain Cauldron is rare.
Now that the war is about to begin, I will use this opportunity
to steal the Rain Cauldron.
It's my best chance to enter the Celestial Realm.
Wang Lin's new look represents Life and Death merged together. The white robes represent Life and his hairpin represents Death.\N\NGradually, more and more carvings flew to him, but at this moment, a black vortex appeared between his hands. Even though the wood carvings went in one by one, the size of the black vortex didn’t change at all. One by one, the wood carvings flew into the black vortex.\N\NThe black vortex quickly changed shapes under Wang Lin’s control. Finally, it turned into a square and gradually became solid. Slowly, the black vortex disappeared and a black stamp appeared before Wang Lin.\N\NThe stamp was the size of Wang Lin’s palm and had the carving of a person on it, but this person didn’t have a face or features, only a figure. This black stamp contained Wang Lin’s 400 years of killing. It was the physical form of Death.\N\NWang Lin’s right hand pressed down on top of the black stamp. A sense of being submerged in blood suddenly appeared in his heart. Then he took a deep breath and the stamp gradually entered his Nascent Soul.\N\N-> Wang Lin wears the same hairpin as the Death wood carving.\N\NWang Lin slowly walked on the street as the snowstorm got even worse.\NHis figure when he walked out from the shop was still that of an old man at the end of his days, but as he walked toward the end of the street, his back gradually straightened. The wrinkles on his face slowly disappeared, and by the time he arrived at the end of the street, he had successfully changed from a mortal to a cultivator.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.